Philip M. Sheppard Papers 1911-1976 1940-1976 Mss.Ms.Coll.65
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1946-1983; 28 boxes, 14 lin. feet
  - Beer, R.J.S., 1967 (Box Series I-2)
  - Begon, Michael, 1974-76 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bell, Betty, 1961 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bellehu, Adefris, 1957 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bellion, Kathleen Patricia, 1972 (Box Series I-2)
  - Belyayev, D.K., 1968 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bengston, Sven-Axel, 1972-75 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bennett, J. Henry, 1961-68 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bennett, M.J., 1953 (Box Series I-2)
  - Benson, A.C., 1972-73 (Box Series I-2)
  - Benson, Woodruff W., 1975-76 (Box Series I-2)
    Turner, John R.G.
    -See also Ser.I, Brown, Keith
  - Bentley, E.W., 1961 (Box Series I-2)
  - Beregovoy, V.E., 1971 (Box Series I-2)
  - Berger, Jacques, 1964 (Box Series I-2)
  - Berio, R., 1952 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bernardi, G., 1963-64 (Box Series I-2)
  - Berry, R.J. (Sam), 1962-76 (Box Series I-2)
    -See also Ser.I, Nuffield Foundation
  - Berry, W.T.C., 1963 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bertie, J., 1964 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bertram, G.C.L. (Box Series I-2)
    -See Ser.I, Eugenics Society
  - Bertram, Horst, 1963-68 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bevan, [?], 1956 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bevan, E. Alan, 1963; 1967 (Box Series I-2)
    -See also Ser.I, Blackwell Scientific Publications, Inc.
  - Billingham, R.E., 1956 (Box Series I-2)
  - Biological Society, 1976 (Box Series I-2)
  - Biometric Society, 1953-56 (Box Series I-2)
  - Birch, L. Charles, 1965-72 (Box Series I-2)
  - Birch, M.W., 1962 (Box Series I-2)
  - Birdsall, D. Alan, 1969-71 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bishop, C.M. (Mrs.), 1964 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bishop, James, 1968 (Box Series I-2)
  - Black, David, 1972 (Box Series I-2)
    -See also Oversized
  - Blackman, Roger L., 1971-72 (Box Series I-2)
  - Blackwell Scientific Publications, Inc. (Box Series I-2)
    Bevan, E. A[lan]
    Reeve, E.C.R.
    - Folder 1, 1959-70 (Box Series I-2)
    - Folder 2, 1971-72 (Box Series I-2)
    - Folder 3, 1973-75 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bland, Desmond S., 1961-73 (Box Series I-2)
  - Blears, J., 1971 (Box Series I-2)
  - Blest, A. David, 1956-58; 1975 (Box Series I-2)
  - Block, W., 1960-61 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bloom, Paul W., Jr., 1973-76 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bloy, F.J., 1959 (Box Series I-2)
  - Board of Trade. Import Licensing Branch, 1952-53 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bobrow, Martin, 1967 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bodmer, Walter F., 1974 (Box Series I-2)
  - Boettger, [?], 1953-54 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bognard, Louis, 1953 (Box Series I-2)
    Some in French
  - Bone, Quentin, n.d. (Box Series I-3)
  - Bonnefoi, Marcel, 1972 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bonnet, David D., 1961; n.d. (Box Series I-3)
  - Boonyotha, P.T., 1966 (Box Series I-3)
  - Booth, Norman, 1968 (Box Series I-3)
    Barnes, W.H.F.
  - Booth, Roger D., 1972 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bösiger, Ernest, 1957 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bourke, G.J., 1954 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bourne, A.M., 1975 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bovey, P., 1952; 1958 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowater, W., 1952; 1960-62 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowden, K.F., 1962 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowden, Sydney R., 1959-72 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowens Camera Repair Service Ltd., 1968 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowers, Alan B., 1972 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowler, K., 1970 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bowman, John C., 1961-64; 1969 (Box Series I-3)
  - Boyes, [?], 1958 (Box Series I-3)
  - Boys Smith, J.S., 1961 (Box Series I-3)
  - Braddock, E.M. (Mrs.), 1967 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bradley, Brenda M., 1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bradley, John, 1974 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bradley, Stuart, [1970?]-74 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bradshaw, A.D., [1961]-76 (Box Series I-3)
    Asmer Seeds Limited
  - Bradshaw, E.A., 1971-76 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brain Research Association, [1974] (Box Series I-3)
  - Bramah, Jean P., 1969 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brambell, F.W. Rogers, 1961-62 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brandt, Jane, 1953 (Box Series I-3)
  - Braunsteiner, H., 1968 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brayhead Products Ltd., 1962 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brent, Leslie, 1968 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bridges, William, 1962 (Box Series I-3)
    Crane, [Jocelyn]
  - Brierley, J.K., 1958-68 (Box Series I-3)
  - Briggs, G.H., 1960 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Association for the Advancement of Science, 1953-75 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 1, 1956-65 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 2, 1965-76 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Cancer Council, [1969] (Box Series I-3)
  - British Council (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 1, 1963-69 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 2, 1970-76 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Embassy (Addis Ababa, Ethiopia), 1957 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Embassy (Manila, Philippines), 1966 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Empire Cancer Campaign, 1954 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Federation of University Women, 1973 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Film Institute, 1962 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Kinematograph, Sound and Television Society, 1973 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Library, 1974 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Medical Bulletin, 1958-60 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Medical Journal, 1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Museum (Natural History), 1956; 1976 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Overseas Airways Corporation, 1958 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Society for Haematology, 1968-69 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Transport Commission, 1957-74 (Box Series I-3)
  - British Universities Film Council Ltd., 1968-76 (Box Series I-3)
  - Britten, Roy J., 1969 (Box Series I-3)
  - Britton, E.B., 1953 (Box Series I-3)
    Ford, E.B.
  - Brncic, Danko, 1958 (Box Series I-3)
  - Broadhead, Edward, 1973 (Box Series I-3)
    -See also Ser.I, Journal of Animal Ecology
  - Broodbank, A.R., 1975 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brooks, G. (Mrs.), 1972 (Box Series I-3)
  - Brower, Jane Van Zandt (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser.I, Brower, Lincoln P.
    -See Ser.I, Van Zandt, Jane
  - Brower, Lincoln P. (Box Series I-3)
    [Brower], Jane Van Zandt
    Glass, Bentley
    O'Donald, Peter
    Thorne, Fred
    - Folder 1, 1954-60 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 2, 1961-62 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 3, 1963-65 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 4, 1966-67 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder 5, 1968 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder 6, 1969-76 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, E.J., 1972 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Keith [S., Jr.] (Box Series I-4)
    Benson, W.[W.]
    The Royal Society
    -See also Ser.I, Turner, John R.G., 1973-75
    - Folder 1, 1956; 1971-73 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder 2, 1973-74 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder 3, 1974 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder 4, 1975 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder 5, 1976 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, R., 1952 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, R.G.B., 1955 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Spencer W., 1973 (Box Series I-4)
  - William C. Brown Co., 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown University, 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brunet, Peter C., 1958; 1968-70 (Box Series I-4)
    -See also Ser.I, Winter, Aline S.
  - Buchanan, O. Marcus, 1968 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buckwalter, Joseph A. (Box Series I-4)
  - Bull, H.O., 1953 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burchnall, H.H., 1963-72 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burges, N. Alan, 1960; 1965 (Box Series I-4)
    -See also Ser.I, Dumbell, Stanley
  - Burke, Frederick, 1973 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burke, Patrick, 1958 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burkhardt, Valentino R., 1953; 1961 (Box Series I-4)
    Hardy, [Alister C.]
  - Burnet, Barrie, 1969-76 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burnett, John H., 1955; 1962 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burns, John M., 1965 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burr, J., 1958-60 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burrows, E.M., n.d. (Box Series I-4)
  - Burt, Davied[?], 1952 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buruga, Joseph H., 1974 (Box Series I-4)
  - Busch, Theo, 1953-54 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bush, Guy L., 1968-69 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bustard, H. Robert, 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - Butler, G.W., 1955 (Box Series I-4)
  - Butler, Roy, 1972-76 (Box Series I-4)
    Roff, Derek Anthony
    -See also Ser.I, Maylor, Ernest
  - Butterfly Preservation Society, 1971 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buxton, Charles, 1968-70 (Box Series I-4)
  - Byrne, [?], 1956 (Box Series I-4)
  - Byrne, O.R., 1967 (Box Series I-4)
  - C.S.I.R.O. (Commonwealth Scientific and Industrial Research Organization), 1966-70 (Box Series I-4)
  - C.Z. Scientific Instruments Ltd., 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cadbury, James, 1964 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cadd, Sylvia, 1966 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cain, Arthur J., 1950-1983; 2 folders (Box Series I-4)
    Cordeiro, A[ntonio] R.
    Harvey, Paul
    Jones, J.S.
    Smith, J.D.D.
    Williams, K.R. (Mrs.)
    -See also Ser.I, Clarke, Bryan
    -See also Ser.I, Diamond, A.W.
    -See also Ser.I, Lamotte, Maxime
    Biographical and personal data; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Evolution; Genetics -- Cats; Genetics -- Snails; Huxley, Julian; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Lectures, public speaking; Mayr, Ernst; Population genetics; Publication; Publication -- Genetics; Simpson, George Gaylord; Teaching; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; Wright, Sewall
    - Folder 1, 1950-1961 (Box Series I-4)
    - Folder 2, 1962-1973; 1983 (Box Series I-4)
  - Callam, [?], 1957 (Box Series I-4)
  - Callan, H.G., 1953-61 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cambridge University Press, 1968-73 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cameron, Robert A.D., 1971 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cammack, R.H., 1957 (Box Series I-4)
  - Campbell, C., 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Canada Council, 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Canada. Dept. of Agriculture, 1961 (Box Series I-4)
  - Canadian Journal of Zoology, 1975 (Box Series I-4)
  - Carcasson, R.H., 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Careers Research and Advisory Centre, 1968-75 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlson, Elof Axel, 1973 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carr, W.J., 1967 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carroll, Robert (Box Series I-5)
  - Carson, Hampton L., 1973 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carson, Meredith, 1955 (Box Series I-5)
    Mrs. Hampton L.
  - Carter, D.J., 1970-71 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, Michael A., 1965-70 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, T.C., 1956-57 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carthy, John D., 1961-67 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cartrefle College of Education, 1967 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cassels, J.M., 1970 (Box Series I-5)
  - Caswell, G.H., 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Catanese, Ronald, 1973 (Box Series I-5)
  - Catcheside, David G., 1960; 1966-71 (Box Series I-5)
  - Catley, A., 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cawkwell, G.L., 1969 (Box Series I-5)
  - Central Office of Information, 1968-69 (Box Series I-5)
  - Ceppellini, R., 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chalkley, John F., 1953 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chambers, Barbara, 1969 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chapman & Hall Ltd., 1971-76 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chanter, D.O., 1973 (Box Series I-5)
  - Charlesworth, Brian, 1971-76 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chase Bank, 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chatterley, Francis, 1953 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chaturvedi, G.C., 1975 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chaun, H., 1955 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chautard, E.A., 1973 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chen, Lee-Ton, 1961 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cheong, Geh Ik, 1960-61 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cheshire County Council. Highways Dept., 1958 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chester Jones, Ian, 1962 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chicago Natural History Museum, 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chitty, Dennis, 1958 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chitty, F. John, 1952-53 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chojnacki, S., n.d. (Box Series I-5)
  - Chowdhury, K.A., 1952 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chown, Bruce, 1960 (Box Series I-5)
  - Christopher, R. (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser.I, Jones, J.W.
  - Ciba Foundation, 1958 (Box Series I-5)
  - CIBA-GEIGY Fellowship Trust, 1972-75 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clarendon Press, 1956-73 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clarke, Ann, 1968; n.d. (Box Series I-5)
    Mrs. Bryan C.
  - Clarke, Bryan C. (Box Series I-5)
    [Cain], Arthur [J.]
    - Folder 1, 1957-66 (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder 2, 1967-76 (Box Series I-5)
  - Clarke, Cyril Astley, 1952-1976; 16 folders (Box Series I-5)
    Adams, Michael J.
    Aird, Ian
    Archer, Richard K.
    [Arnott], Melville
    Bateman, Angus
    Beazley, John M.
    Bishop, James
    Black, D.
    Bowden, Sydney
    Buckwalter, Joseph A.
    Carroll, Robert
    Chown, Bruce
    Collins, Stephen
    Cook, [Laurence M.]
    Davey, M.G.
    Descimon, H.
    Diamond, Louis K.
    Doll, Richard
    Douglas of Barloch
    Downie, A.W.
    Dransfield, J.W.
    Eliot, J.
    Emslie, R.D.
    Finn, Ronald
    Ford, C.E.
    Ford, E.B. (1955)
    Fraser Roberts, J.A.
    Friedhoff, Arnold J.
    Glynn, L.E.
    Gunaratne, V.T.H.
    Harrison, Geoffrey Ainsworth
    Hughes Jones, N.C.
    Johnson, J.H.
    Karunaratne, P.B.
    Kay, Andrew M. (1955)
    Kellett, D.N.
    King, J.O.L.
    Kinlen, Leo
    Knudsen, John P.
    Krevans, Julius R.
    Langman, Michael J.S.
    Lehane, D.
    Leonard, Warren H.
    Lorkovic, Z.
    McKendrick, Olive
    MacNicholas, J.
    McO[?]var, P.B.
    Maessen, [?] (Rev. Father)
    Mattoni, R.H.T.
    Maycock, W. d'A.
    Moor-Jankowski, Jan K.
    Moorhead, [?]
    Morton, Newton E.
    Murray, [?]
    Naylor, M.N.
    Nuffield Foundation
    Olivier-Wright, Anabel
    Patel, A.R.
    Paulian, Renaud
    Pearson, Peter
    Peebles Brown, D.A. (1955)
    Penrose, L.S.
    Polani, Paul E.
    Pollack, William
    Porter, R.R.
    Remington, Charles
    Roche, Patrick
    Rogers, Stephen Clifford
    [Rothschild?], Miriam
    Royal Entomological Society of London
    Sanger, Ruth
    Scali, Valerio
    Smithells, Richard W.
    Stern, Kurt
    Todd, Pat
    Valletta, Anthony
    van Rood, J.J.
    van Someren, V.G.L.
    Vesco, J.-P.
    Vosa, C.
    Walsh, Niall P.
    Warburton, Frederick E.
    Watanabe, Masato
    White, G.A.
    Whittle, Peter D.J.
    Wiedemann, [?]
    Wiener, Alexander S.
    Wilson, Kent H.
    Woodrow, John C.
    Worms, Charles
    Wynne-Davies, Ruth
    Zeuner, F.E.
    Zipursky, A.
    -See also Ser.I, Cain, Arthur J.
    -See also Ser.I, Cockayne, E.A.
    -See also Ser.I, Ford, E.B. (1963)
    -See also Ser.I, Gray, G.
    -See also Ser.I, Macdonald, W.W. (1970)
    -See also Ser.I, Pumphrey, Alison
    -See also Ser.I, Remington, Charles L.
    -See also Ser.I, Rothschild, Miriam
    -See also Ser.I, Van Someren, V.G.L.
    -See also Ser.I, Watson, Christabel
    -See also Ser.I, Wells, M.J.
    -See also Ser.I, West, David
    -See also Ser.I, Whittle, Peter D.J.
    Cancer, chemotherapy; Embryology, developmental genetics; Evolution; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Human genetics; Human genetics -- Blood groups; Photographs; Population genetics; Publication; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
    - Folder 1, 1952 (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder 2, 1953 (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder 3, 1954 (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder 4, 1955 (Box Series I-5)
    - Folder 5, 1956 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 6, 1957-1962 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 7, 1963-1964 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 8, 1965 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 9, 1966-1967 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 10, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 11, 1969 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 12, 1970-1972 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 13, 1973 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 14, 1974 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 15, 1975 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder 16, 1976; n.d. (Box Series I-6)
  - Clarke, F.M.M., 1964; 1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clarke, K.U., 1972-73 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clarke, Stephen, 1965 (Box Series I-6)
  - Claux, R.H., 1953 (Box Series I-6)
  - Claxton, P.P., 1973 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clegg, John, 1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clements, C.N.A., 1956 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clements, D.J.M., 1955 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clench, Harry K., 1953 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clifford, H.T., 1956 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clifton, O. (Mrs.), 1956 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clowes, Royston C., 1966-73 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cock, A.G., 1963 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cockayne, E.A., 1953-54 (Box Series I-7)
    Clarke, [Cyril A.]
  - Coe, Malcolm, 1973 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cogley, Kathleen M., 1974-75 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cold Spring Harbor Biological Association, 1959 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cole, R.K., 1960-63 (Box Series I-7)
    -See also Ser.I, Werrett, W.F.
  - Cole, Thomas A., 1975-76 (Box Series I-7)
  - Collier-Macmillan Ltd., 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Collin, H.A., 1969 (Box Series I-7)
  - Collinge, Brian, 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Collins, Charles T., 1963 (Box Series I-7)
  - Collins, Stephen, 1975 (Box Series I-7)
  - Collinson, Richard I., 1971 (Box Series I-7)
  - Columbia University Press, 1971 (Box Series I-7)
  - Comfort, Ann, 1956 (Box Series I-7)
  - Comunale, Gertrude, 1960; 1967 (Box Series I-7)
  - Conn, David Lindsay Thurburn, 1967; 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Conroy, Brian A., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - Constable and Company, Ltd., 1961 (Box Series I-7)
  - Conway, Gordon R., 1971-73 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cook, E.R. (Box Series I-7)
    -See Ser.I, Angseesing, Joseph
  - Cook, Laurence M. (Box Series I-7)
    -See also Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril A. (16 June 1960)
    -See also Ser.I, Ford, E.B. (1961)
    -See also Ser.I, Johnson, J.H.
    - Folder 1, 1958-62 (Box Series I-7)
    - Folder 2, 1963-76 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cooks (Tho[ma]s Cook & Son, Ltd.), 1967-73 (Box Series I-7)
  - Coombs, R.R.A. (Box Series I-7)
    -See Ser.I, Cowan, W.K.
  - Cooper, Beowulf A., 1965-68 (Box Series I-7)
  - Coote, P.R., 1974 (Box Series I-7)
  - Coppinger, Raymond P., 1967 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cordeiro, Antonio R., 1954; 1970-74 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cornmarket Press Ltd., 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cowan, W.K., 1961 (Box Series I-7)
    Coombs, R.R.A.
  - Cox, D.T., 1958 (Box Series I-7)
  - Craggs, John D., 1968; 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Craggs, Susan, 1967-69 (Box Series I-7)
  - Craig, H., 1962 (Box Series I-7)
  - Craig, Sally P., 1969 (Box Series I-7)
  - Craig-Cameron, T.A., 1973 (Box Series I-7)
  - Crane, Jocelyn, 1956-65 (Box Series I-7)
    -See also Ser.I, Bridges, William
  - Crawford, Martin d'A., 1971-72 (Box Series I-7)
  - Crean, E.A., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - Creaser, Alan, 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Creed, E. Robert, 1959-74 (Box Series I-7)
  - Crew County Grammer School for Girls, 1973 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cribb, P.W., 1963 (Box Series I-7)
  - Crick, Francis H. C., 1962; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-7)
    Molecular genetics; Publication -- Discovery; Requests for reprints
  - Croft, James, 1970-73 (Box Series I-7)
  - Crosby, J[ack] L., 1960-76 (Box Series I-7)
  - Crowe, Joan P., 1971 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cullerne, A.C., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cunliffe, [?], 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Curio, E., 1973 (Box Series I-7)
  - Curnow, Robert N., 1967-68 (Box Series I-7)
  - Currey, John, 1955; 1961-76 (Box Series I-7)
  - Curtis, C.F., 1968-71 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cushing, P.H., 1973 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cutler, David F., 1975 (Box Series I-7)
  - da Cuhna, Brito, 1965 (Box Series I-7)
  - Daday, H., 1970 (Box Series I-7)
  - The Daily Mail, 1956; 1965 (Box Series I-7)
  - The Daily Mirror, 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dales, R.P., 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Danielli, J.F., 1952 (Box Series I-7)
  - Darbey, J., 1974-75 (Box Series I-7)
  - Darlington, Cyril Dean, 1951-1961; 1969; 14.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-7)
    Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; Physiology; Requests for reprints; Reviews; Wigglesworth, Vincent B.
  - Darlington, P.J., Jr., 1964 (Box Series I-7)
  - da Silva Cruz, A., 1952 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davenport, Margaret, 1968 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davenport, Demorest, 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davey, M.G. (Box Series I-7)
    See Ser.I, Clarke, Cyril A.
  - David, Peter M., 1960 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davidson, Douglas (Box Series I-7)
  - Davidson, P.S.W., 1955 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davies, Clifford E., 1967-69 (Box Series I-7)
    Tinbergen, Niko
    Walker, Stanley
  - Davies, D.R., n.d. (Box Series I-7)
    -See also Ser.I, Turner, John
  - Davies, Elwyn, 1961 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davies, G.O., 1961 (Box Series I-7)
    Baxter, J.T.
  - Davies, John, 1955; 1964 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davies, Lewis, 1976 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davies, Noel A., 1964 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davis, B.N.K., 1972 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davis, T.C., 1952 (Box Series I-7)
  - Davis, W.H. (Mrs.), 1974 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dawe, R.J., 1967 (Box Series I-7)
  - Dawson, George W.P., 1960-73 (Box Series I-7)
  - Day, C.[L.], 1957 (Box Series I-7)
  - Daymond, S.D., 1960 (Box Series I-7)
  - Deakin, [?] (Miss), n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - de Andrade, N.F., 1951-52 (Box Series I-8)
  - de Araújo, Aldo Mellender, 1973-76 (Box Series I-8)
  - de Beer, Gavin, 1956-68 (Box Series I-8)
  - de Castro, A.F., 1971 (Box Series I-8)
  - Degenhardt & Company Ltd., 1969 (Box Series I-8)
  - Degner, E., 1954 (Box Series I-8)
    Some inGerman
  - De Laney, Carole, 1965; 1968 (Box Series I-8)
  - Delaney, Steve, 1976 (Box Series I-8)
  - Demerec, M. (Milislav), 1955-1959; 5.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-8)
    Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory; Conferences and symposia; Darwin, Charles; Drosophila Information Service; Invitations; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Dempster, Everett R., 1969 (Box Series I-8)
    Kimura, Motoo
  - Dennell, Ralph, 1969 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dennison, Sheena, 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dept. of Education and Science, 1969-73 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dept. of Scientific and Industrial Research, 1960; 1964 (Box Series I-8)
  - Derby Hall. The Warden, 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - De Rover, W., 1972 (Box Series I-8)
  - de Ruiter, Leen, 1953-62 (Box Series I-8)
  - Desai, R.G., 1960-61 (Box Series I-8)
  - Descimon, H., 1964-68 (Box Series I-8)
  - de Scusa, D. Gabriel, 1962 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dhesi, Sohan Singh, 1966 (Box Series I-8)
  - Diamond, A.W., 1970 (Box Series I-8)
    Cain, [Arthur J.]
  - Diamond, Louis K. (Box Series I-8)
  - Dictionary of International Biography, 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dillon, Lawrence S., 1971-72 (Box Series I-8)
  - Discovery, 1963 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dluhy, Eugene, 1955 (Box Series I-8)
  - Samuel Dobie & Son, Ltd., 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1953-1971; 2 folders (Box Series I-8)
    -See also Ser.I, Johnson, George
    Biographical and personal data; Cain, Arthur James; Carson, Hampton L.; Clarke, Cyril Astley; Columbia University; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Royal Society (Great Britain); Crow, James F.; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships; Ford, Edmund Brisco; Genetics -- Butterflies, moths; International Congress of Genetics; Kimura, Motoo; Levene, Howard; Population genetics; Publication; Publication -- American Naturalist; Requests for reprints; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
    - Folder 1, 1953-1961 (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder 2, 1962-1971 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dodd, J., 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dodsworth, E., 1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Doll, Richard (Box Series I-8)
  - Dommée, Bertrand, 1974-76 (Box Series I-8)
  - [Donald], Robert G., n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Doud, [?], 1962 (Box Series I-8)
  - Douglas, Linda M., 1967-68 (Box Series I-8)
  - Douglas, [Mick], [1975] (Box Series I-8)
  - Douglas of Barloch, Francis Campbell Ross Douglas (Lord), 1974 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dowdeswell, Wilfred H., 1958; 1964-71; n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Downes, Antony, 1964 (Box Series I-8)
  - Downham, David Y., 1970; 1975 (Box Series I-8)
  - Downie, A.W. (Box Series I-8)
  - Dransfield, J.W., 1964-72 (Box Series I-8)
    Mills, C.P.J.
    Scudamore, James M.
  - Drewett, Pauline Margaret, 1970-71 (Box Series I-8)
  - Drosophila Information Service, 1970 (Box Series I-8)
  - Drummond, David C., 1963; 1966 (Box Series I-8)
    Falconer, D.S.
  - Dubuisson, M., 1964 (Box Series I-8)
    Some inFrench
  - Dufrane, Alec, 1952 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dumbell, Stanley, 1957-60 (Box Series I-8)
    Burges, N.A.
    -See also Ser.I, Lloyds Bank Ltd.
  - Dun, G.S., 1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Duncan, Chris J., 1965-72 (Box Series I-8)
  - Duncan, J.G., 1956-57 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dunn, L.C., 1956 (Box Series I-8)
  - Dunn-Coleman, N., 1972 (Box Series I-8)